yo you know webscoe p fam gather
insurance we're getting we're getting
real good at this now alright so this is
my first time driving the open pilot
port to the fusion here I here are you
know it says magnified stop let's end
the upload right is officially canceled
okay guys the fourth thing might be fake
news I kind of think they're just
posturing against Trump's Mexico
George why don't we have the cool up so
we got our door for you started again I
know it's good alright why don't we have
the cool what holder for your phone
difference for people lordy zip it on
that alright
sorry periscope smokey so we crashed a
new Ford Fusion
no but they be experiencing it yeah
who's in the car it's me Riccardo and
George yeah it's like a fun mountain -
the sunroof totally agreed that would
look great no let me out some air
conditioning in this car so hot yeah
this is reminding me that's more
weak-ass Ford oh that's better now
we're talking I just hear it I feel good
Ricardo a little kind of laptop so I was
wondering what predator yeah this is
reminding me of the good old days in the
rav4 when we drove across the country
and this was just a way to hold the
scope he's at all times wanna show them
for giraffe
yeah look at our four giraffe
large engage this thing so you need to
first turn on the on yes okay it does
something it does something but then it
cuts out now we can try the root of one
because now there is a new combination
this could be worse so yeah there's some
there's some issues with the fork or
what do you psi I told the scope is that
that's a new band question guys EPS exit
dangerous don't mess with EPS x/y Chevy
well so you guys know that we paid out
the Volt port but we haven't up streamed
it yet there's a lot of subtlety to the
the safety we want to make sure we get
it right so we are going to buy a Chevy
you can guess what carcass contesse it's
a dad car
scope is now
they're not guessing it without guessing
both Chevy Volt na debug alert why is
there debug alert because we are like a
low speeds and so it's not allowed it's
not a lot of low speed eleven twelve
miles per hour
okay Demian just like my rev no your rap
doesn't have a stop a gun with Lisa
fusion he'll stop and go the ACC in this
car is very good
oh it's very good with you oh this one
is stop and go yes Sona stopping go yeah
so we're want ACC right now except you
have to press the button to resume which
kind of sucks is this one easy to
overcome yeah because like we can't send
what we can send that we can stay on the
buttons oh that's a good deal if you
have open viola we can just spam the
actual pun I mean I was doing it there
for the bathroom but I was already was
closing fault but I don't think it was
disabled now that's low torque if we
just get like a hundred thousand more
super hearts movie good we can be part
of the periscope famous people program
Oh be like just like Casey nice dad
exactly yeah he's not a periscope right
he's all right so that that's where
that's your half cents yes pumping yes
copies what what GMO were you going to
buy people guessed it but a lot of
people are saying the Impala we thought
about an Impala turns out Jonah Bevan
times our GM sells 720 and follows a
month well if you want a Buick LaCrosse
then they only sell seven
the Cadillac Wow you know hey they just
got one in stock
what if they sold it to folks oh it's
just for me so I know when the lot of
control is cut out by the EPS you have
the 40 PS before the PS so yes as a
problem every 10 seconds it stops
responding and so it's not the best
control starting with but then every 10
seconds they throw out like temporary a
fault that you had like to disable
control and then they like really you to
to commend new things now there are like
a ton of other modes another flag that
you can send and I like a lot of
combinations so there is still hope for
that we might overcome this is like 10
second timeout but so far not so good
there's a lot of modes it's very
complicated oh it's doing so okay we did
something there the pork wasn't that bad
yeah
oh I don't like oh it's not a total
cancellation mode I disabled it there's
a now if you want to engage it oh why
doesn't this go plus because your stuff
I can't put the blocking out for the
speed-up free config world is garbage
no because it's like overloaded we did a
Sumatra I understand alright great Ford
whomp it check out our Ford giraffes in
fact as a peasant at its really how do
you made it yeah long-long like a Ford
it's very funny steer back there back
there back there back
oh man that's all act yo this is my butt
yeah I have like a second masticating
for real well so the problem is that the
interface it seems like it's angled
phaser
yeah then if you provide like an angle
based interface at least the job in -
yeah so what we had what I think that
even though both for both torque rotor
angle nest yes it really seems like
everything is that because the well so
that's the problem
while I'm eating I have stuff for you so
you're getting that from the radar okay
yeah yeah don't like 64 objects that's
nice super noisy but yeah yeah the
Dolphy has a motel
it's like 60 no I'm just beautiful on
your name is autumn
looks like it does look like autumn yeah
yeah multi cause I like that I'm like
half engage now I'm so confused
and it's a little bit better higher
speed because I could was are there any
Chinese
zero counter love for ping pong yang
that this is even like it doesn't even
try
was that your breaker that was the car
is good it's not open file doing that
guys I'm about to doing steering but
okay so here's our hope for the GM we
think that it's the same platform as
super horse so we think super cruise is
using the same like interface and super
cruise is good so our goal for the end
of the year with open piled 0.5 is to
surpass both super cruise and autopilot
we're trying to be like a superset of
both of them well we'll see I think we
can beat the current test log day
we'll see if Tesla keeps updating
supercruise things that we have to ship
to match supercruise our driver
monitoring and supercruise does not
wobble it is zero wobble guys I remember
when it was fun to buy cars now it's at
work someone has swine flu she's sorry
I'm happy that we can I know I was about
I was thinking that - Tesla showroom
showroom reject repeat Alamo GM you
don't understand guys okay Tesla owns
all their dealerships so they can ban us
GM is not really affiliated with this GM
dealership it's like a bunch of bros who
buy cars from GM so as much as GF might
not like me it doesn't matter cuz this
guy like what does he can't just own the
car he's just gonna be like the classic
like Bob cool very cool for a company Ok
Go your guys my lieutenants secret to
buy cars negotiate the price down and
then tell them you know about incentives
and rebates and then pretend you know
more about rebates than they know
yo yo Toyota was trying to lie to us oh
that did something
yeah you know but like it cuts out so
long
well this is usable almost almost
lag
yeah okay so this is an example of a
steering control a class ii
laughs well
these cases so prob
the scope he's know we're doing very
exciting stuff for Oakland of zero point
five point six and if a zero for point
four point seven we're finally going to
focus on a moving wall oh so exciting so
exciting you know sometimes an open
pilot feedback you know we never thought
of that
yeah you know now that you bring it up
so that's why we're working on it for
zero point four point seven
I really don't engage
this is this this system is normal car
I'll cast quality so we managed up the
Ford from nothing to normal L chemist
it's sad there's no reason any of this
should be lacked like there's the
Lancaster where does the lack even come
from
they have like most likely means of in
force
I know these bots are copy or comments
I'm sorry I'll ban on the next time I
see them just
how does periscope up to a little better
you know now that we have accepted that
all these companies are content
moderation platforms
do you know anything is that you can't
hurt a boss feelings you know like you
get an inner win when you ban but then
you realize like wait they don't care
that that's right that's why no
straining yeah that's why we all have to
stop being so outraged you're probably
arguing with a bottom yeah the person
who has very strong different views from
you is probably literally a bot designed
to make you out rich
do I see their driver monitor monitor so
we're going back to the same GM
dealership that let me test-drive
supercruise so I get a little bit of
good points for them Oh George you are
about apparently according to warrant
are you sure you're not confusing me
with mr. Zuckerberg in the same you know
just because I'm wearing a grey hoodie
man Oh way if they go pick up our new
hoodies
you're very employees afraid of boys
only that's right that's right you can't
buy hoodies yeah um but always stay
tuned for the special merch drops being
Jorge from Twitter oh my gosh how could
you say oh I don't even tweet what just
cuz my name is real George Hobbs oh shut
up follow me on twitter also check of a
sack claps a concise Tom Cruise I'm
aspiring rapper from the suburbs
this camera quality is pretty nice they
have like a like our lighting has been
good for most of the ride we start with
the iPhone X yeah oh yeah that's so
great yeah
all right Stuart Chevrolet brought to
you by Stuart Chevrolet this stretch is
so weird it's just like babies are out
babies are us going out of business
classic babies are going to not just
toys I just want to see if we can park
electric vehicle parking only sure we're
a hybrid we have some electric yes
Turner we park the electric that nice
Jim let you used should we bring him in
let's go please oh no we gotta be normal
yeah thank you for joining thank you for
joining there's a real subdued day you
know chill day today yeah we'll let you
guys know yeah well we'll be scope
Maurice cope by